Curriculum Vitae

SUMMARY

I had studied programming while in college, and decided to further develop my programming skills, especially in web programming. I have over 1 years of experience as an Frontend Developer and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach

INFORMATION

Full Name : Akhsan Bayu Riantama

Place, Date of Birth : Jayapura, 3 February 1999

Gender : Male

Address : Jl. Kopeng KM 5, Tegalrejo, Magelang

Email : akhsanby@gmail.com

EDUCATION

STMIK Bina Patria, Kota Magelang - S.Kom

October 2017 - Desember 2021

I am graduated as Informatics Engineering student with GPA 3.49 by producing a final assignment about simple artificial intelligence

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Digireg Indonesia - Frontend Developer

March 2022 - February 2023

Im work in IT Development as Frontend Developer to develop WebGIS interface

EXPERTISE AND SKILLS

Programing Language

PHP, Javascript

Framework / Library

Laravel, Codelgniter, VueJS, ReactJS

Design Tools

Corel Draw, Inkscape, Figma

TRAINING & COURSE

Course Coding Online in Dicoding Academy

2020 - Present

I have passed some lessons from Frontend and Backend learning path

Course Coding Online in Udemy

2023 - Present

Im currently studying Golang & Laravel

Kampus Merdeka with Hacktiv8

August 2021 – February 2022

I learn more about Frontend Development, React and React Native

SOCIAL MEDIA

Github - https://github.com/akhsanby

Personal web - https://akhsanby.vercel.app

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/akhsanby